Come on, we're shining, running, forever!
The sea is calling out, so ride the waves!
We're all together as one,
so let's sail in the sun!
All our dreams are never-ending, so
let's wake up, wake up, wake up, wake up!
Heartbeat, we will be one! Go ahead!
Even though our hearts have
traveled different paths.
We are best friends.
Our freedom is our only compass.
That's pointing us along the
many roads that come together.
We will keep on running forward every day.
Go east, go west.
As long as we keep looking to the horizon.
We'll see everything all crystal clear.
We're all so thrilled that we
can't wait until the dawn arrives.
So we'll just bring the
sun ourselves to know.
If the winds blow, it's waiting
where we should be going, go.
That's right, we're
shining, running forever.
All of our dreams will
merge into one piece.
No matter where we go,
we'll be fine and free.
Cause all our treasure is our strength.
Come on, we're shining, running forever.
The sea is coming out, so ride away!
We're all together as well, so
let's just stay with us, son!
All our dreams are never ending, so
let's wake up, wake up, wake up, wake up!
Heartbeat, we will be one, go hey!
My darkness will swallow the
world, just you wait and see!
You think I'll lose to you?
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!
Roger's treasure belongs to me!
We'll ride non-stop and travel farther
than we've ever gone And then tomorrow we
will find suspense And then commence to
live out another day so intense
That's right, we're shining,
running forever Let's go along
with curiosity Our feelings lead
the way straight to a brand new day Into
another adventure Come on, we're shining,
running forever Open the map inside your
heart and see No matter where we end up,
our mods will never give up There's a
fire in our dreams and you can never,
never, never, never stop it
We will be one, go ahead!
It's a dream come true!
This is sure to be the finest
battle you've ever seen!
The four winners from the first round
will be facing each other as well as Mr.
Diamante!
These brave battlers, seeking strength,
shall fight it when they
lay claim to the prize.
Alone ye a Devil Fruit, the strongest of
the three types, the flame flame fruit!
Ha ha!
I can almost taste it!
Stop the match now!
Take Rebecca out of the ring!
Redo the block D match! Oh?
A last-minute objection to the fight?
whatever the hell happened
back there I don't accept
it now fight me there's
no way all of us lost to
a rotten little shrimp
like you time for us to set
the record straight hell
yeah you guys kick your ass
out of the way buddy don't
be such sore losers gentlemen
better to let it go Because
if you ruin my event,
you're gonna be sorry.
Take me down to the perilous. Screw you!
Olé.
Keep it coming.
What?
You think this is a bullfart?
It may ripple like an ordinary cape,
but this is made of solid steel.
I ate the ripple ripple
fruit and became a flag man.
You see all it takes is
one touch And I can make
anything even my own
body flutter like a flag.
Lock.
This is corridor Kalifa.
I.
Get moving, if I were you gentlemen!
They love the smell of blood, they're
fine-tuned to it you might say.
It's flying!
Oh, wow!
You get a good look at that?
Those fighting fish don't hold back!
They're only supposed to attack
once you fall in the water.
But these guys are rule-breakers. Why,
the fish in the first round are practically
mild matter compared to these savages.
We handpicked the strongest fighter
from each school just for this battle.
If you look carefully, you'll see that
one of them has a surprise on his back.
A treasure chest which holds none
other than the Flake Flake Roots.
the rules of the finals
are simple stay in the
ring and take the fruit
from the back of the fish to
claim victory it's finally
here the match you've all
been waiting for it'll be
a five-man battle royale
including our hero diamante
they must avoid the
wrath of the deadly fighting
fish and scramble to snag
the treasure who among
these fighters will lay
claim to the flame flame
fruit and now let the battle
begin
nice let's go
Is that how you get inside the palace?
The palace is above us.
That's the Rampart Tower.
Thankfully, the Rampart
Tower has a secret entrance.
Let's go, but take care not
to let the guards notice you.
They'll call the executives
if we make a scene.
That won't be good.
Especially if we have to battle with Pika.
Then any hope of success would be lost.
Where is Sir Luffy?
Uh-oh, right there.
Whoa, what's up with that hoop?
Now, Gum-Gum!
Maybe it's actually a
blue fish? That's freaky!
Giant pitfall!
What the hell is he doing?
It's open.
That's not the issue here.
This is not good.
You get lucky. Well, new plan.
We're going in.
If we hurry, we might get lucky.
Can I take this thing off now?
Not like I could stop you. Now, now.
Oh, Straw Hat?
Straw Hat Luffy has broken in!
The fighting fish attacks, but
Lucy leaps aside with ease!
Nobody else has moves like that!
What the hell is going on here?
You're sure it was Straw Hat Luffy? Yeah!
He smashed the gate in with one punch!
I think you should get your eyes checked.
Straw Hat's fighting in the Coliseum.
He's in disguise, but it's sloppy.
This is from our tower, me too,
in front of the main dining hall!
I'm confusing myself!
Straw Hat Luffy is from the intruders!
He's with pirate hunter Sauron.
And wait, Lady Violet!
Straw Hat Luffy broke into the tower.
And who the hell is that idiot!
With this stupid disguise
fighting in the Coliseum!
Can somebody tell me what's going on?
You bastard!
Come now!
He's too fast for me to see.
You hopeless little fools.
This old man too quick for you?
If you must know, I'll clue you in.
We really didn't expect any
executives to take the lift.
When I received an order to protect
the entrance to the toy house,
I got a little mixed up.
I accidentally rode the
lift all the way down.
So I waited at the trade port floor
until I could ride it up again.
Took a bit, but I got back on.
Now I'm here taking it to
get back to the ground floor.
Floor G!
I won't let you anywhere near
the palace, infiltrators.
No.
We won't be stopped.
Straw Hat Luffy is currently
at B1 of the Rampart Tower.
Which way? The left.
I'm coming, Mingo.
The coast is clear.
I guess security can't keep up.
It's huge!
A wall monster! Not quite. It's Pika!
That's a dude?
What's his deal?
He's a top executive.
A stone assimilation man.
Great, and we get to deal with him.
He's a power holder.
He ate the stone stone fruit.
You see?
So he controls the walls?
So, he's not just a guy made of bricks.
He can merge with stone
itself and control it.
Then it becomes his own body.
Which means the palace
itself has become our enemy.
the walls.
and another ruthless
fighting fish wants in.
oh it's on now.
did that bloodthirsty
fish catch him off guard?
Come on, fishy!
Shockwave!
Alma!
The whole Coliseum is feeling that one!
That was the massive hole in the sand!
His special move, the
shockwave in the boat,
certainly leaves us all
waking up in our boots!
Hailing from the Blackbeard Pirate Crew,
he's one of their ten titanic captains.
Jesus Burgess has just shown us firsthand.
he's truly a force of nature!
He's dangerous.
Looks like another fighting
fish has reared its ugly fin!
I wonder who he's got his eyes on!
Oh, take a look at that!
It's the Fishbox O-1 carrying the
much-lusted Asperger treasure chest!
There it is.
He's locked under the mail!
Just kidding!
Our fish friend has had a change of plans!
Who is he going for?
Are you all seeing this?
Just who is O-1 targeting?
Oh, he's going for America!
It must have been sticking
her arm from the gate ago!
I need to cut the chain at least!
Nice!
I've got you now! Think again!
It's mine!
Here comes the fierce face-off
between Lucy and Diamante!
Straw Hats!
Don't forget about me!
I'll knock you and that fish
out in one shot—get ready!
That flame, flame fruit belongs to me.
Ron burgess is prepping the elbow.
My
barrier isn't here to protect
you—not gonna run, lucy!
run lucy
Tuck wave coming up!
Eat this! Dragon claw!
Well, all be damned!
Burgesses of ours have
shattered into pieces!
Oh, badass!
I'm so proud of you!
Don't want to give me the fruit?
If that's what you get,
I'm not gonna lose.
Seems like his fighting
style changed suddenly.
Did Straw Hat swap with somebody else?
Toys are coming out one after the other.
Sugar is making them.
We were right.
She's in the tower.
What are those tentacle things up there?
There's an exclusive lift for
the executives in the middle.
But those pipes on the sides are where
big people and broken toys get tossed in.
They all lead here, but those giant chutes
can be found everywhere in Dressrosa.
When someone falls through one,
they'll drop past us and streak to a
scrap heap below the executive tower.
Revolting.
First I'm thrown into
the garbage and now this?
It seems I've fallen into a trap.
And a slimy one, unfortunately.
Should have known something was amiss
when they took me to the medical room.
I wasn't even hurt, after all.
It's not slangy, big silly. It's sticky.
Whoa! Hello!
What is this place?
It's the executive tower.
Also, it's where toys come from,
though outsiders wouldn't understand.
But since you're here, you're
not really an outsider, huh?
So we might as well tell you the other
name we have for this special room.
Sugar!
Tell him for me.
I don't care.
Why?
Look what you did.
It's a double snot rope.
Just die. You're gross.
No, you die.
Sorry, but I don't take orders
from little brats like you.
Can you help me, kid? I'm stuck.
Gotta get this sticky goo off of me.
Here's your contract.
You will not do harm to any human.
And you will follow all
orders from the family.
I'm confused, and wait—what
happened to my body?
Changed me back.
Stop talking and get to work.
Okay, I can't talk.
Why am I obeying this idiot?
And you will follow all
orders from the family.
The contract—one more thing.
Nobody remembers you.
remembers you
Even I forgot who you were a second ago.
Now you're going to work for Dofie until
you break down and we
have to throw you away.
How is this happening?
I'm some kind of toy slave.
Keep walking straight till you
hit the port, then get to work.
Oh, new guy.
I'll show you where to go.
Is this a port?
Keep moving.
Here, now get to work
I'm a pirate, dammit What
kind of nightmare is this?
And how do I wake up?
There, your box.
Now go.
No, these toys are creepy.
I don't want to be one of them.
And I especially don't want
to slave away until I die.
So this is where they trade the
weapons to the warring nations.
But I'm powerless to stop it.
I'm helping them.
This is just the lead we were looking for.
If only I had a transponder snail.
Koala's waiting for me.
There must be some way to regain control.
Curse you, Doflamingo.
I'm the king of protents.
Work as a toy till I break down?
Is that a joke?
Somebody help me!
That must be Sugar talking to Trouble.
She really is a kid. In appearance.
Anyway, we know she loves grapes.
She eats them constantly.
And why do I care?
We have a plan.
And a secret weapon!
Looks like a grape, but it's
a clump of Tata Babasco.
It's the hottest spice in the world!
Hold on, you're gonna make her eat it?
We just have to sneak it into the basket.
We tested it before on
50 people from our tribe.
All of them were knocked out
cold and 18 of them almost died
That sounds bad it better
be we can't take any risk
Okay, Leo go.
I'll be watching you from here.
I feel stronger already If this
goes south, I'm cutting out.
Good luck, Leo!
Shut up! Are you crazy?
Don't let Trouble notice you!
Be careful!
Hey!
They're gonna kill you!
This is just the start.
Everyone, prepare yourselves.
The moment that Sugar screams is the
moment when every toy in the kingdom.
regains their human form at long last.
And the other citizens will
reclaim their lost memories.
The truth of this land will be revealed.
All of Doflamingo's evil will
be dragged out into the light!
We will save our friends
and dress Rosa as well!
I told you!
You're too loud!
King Rick will claim
this kingdom once more!
Please shut up!
They're gonna hear you!